## MIDESTINE WALDRON

MY-DESTINY WALL-DRUN

# UX/UI DESIGNER

## PROFILE

UX/UI Designer with nine years of experience enhancing customer relationships as evidenced by interacting with over 2,000 customers. Experience in allocating resources, and improving customer and user experience. Seeking to use a passion for creativity and leadership as displayed by training employees with previous companies. Seeking an organization where creativity is encouraged and results rewarded.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

# **Data Entry/Analysis**

**Procraft Cabinetry** 

Feb 2022-Sep 2022

- Assigned and responsible for 15 clients, generating over 3 million dollars in annual revenue.
- Creatively enhanced sales by 5% through marketing awareness of other branches, during times of low inventory.
- Enhanced sales using creativity and innovation. Creatively enhanced revenue through innovation by enhancing customer awareness.
- Created & refined an electronic system identifying customers, and payment information reducing paper waste
- Simultaneously kept track of customer order requests, coordinated and recorded said requests using a data entry platform and Microsoft Excel

### **Customer Service Representative**

Red Lobster, Bahama Breeze, American Deli Mar 2015-Mar 2020

- · Selected to train and supervise new employees
- Increased restaurant sales by 25% due to suggestive selling and listening to customers underlying wants and desires
- Used experience in allocating resources to enrich customer expectations and experience by engaging with over 2,000 customers through collaboration and listening skills
- Demonstrated exceptional multitasking skills as a hostess by answering customer questions, providing accommodations, and promoting the restaurant policy and expectations
- Explored different methods of organization to fulfill and pack customer orders allowing for minimal space-consumption

### **PROJECTS**

Olive Responsive Web Application (2022-23): Physical & mental health tracking application

MiLexis (2022): Language vocabulary prototype

# CONTACT

404-477-9285

www.linkedin.com/in/midestine-waldron

🤈 Atlanta, Georgia

## TOOLS

Figma Microsoft Office Sublime Text Coding

Marvel

Sketch

User Research

User Testing

A/B Testing

Prototyping

# SOFT SKILLS

**Problem-Solving:** Recognize & acknowledge inconveniences

Adaptability: Acclimate well to change

**Time-Management:** Worked 40 hour work week while completing 25hr school week

**Empathetic:** Respect and create accommodations

Integrity: Accountable for mistakes

Conflict Resolution: Emphasize communication & listening

**Detail-Oriented:** Value uniformity and creativity

## EDUCATION

### **UX Design Certification**

CareerFoundry

2022-2023

- Created a responsive and interactive physical and mental health app, Olive
- Utilized both user testing and research to tailor created app, Olive to user liking in a manner that is both physically accessible, comprehensible, and aesthetically pleasing

# High School Diploma, Allied Healthcare Discovery High School 2016-2020

 Graduated with a Healthcare Seal allowing for a fast track into the medical field